<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on My Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://floriskappeyne.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on My Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://floriskappeyne.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Arboreal</title>
      <link>https://floriskappeyne.github.io/post/meadow-folk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://floriskappeyne.github.io/post/meadow-folk/</guid>
      <description>This video cannot be played.  The project Arboreal is an open-world farming and adventuring game where you save ancient colossi from a spreading corruption. This game was my 3rd year project at the NHTV Breda. Its production started in September 2017 and continued until the end of that school year (July 2018). It is the longest project I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on so far, and it also was the biggest team: we started with 30 people, but this steadily grew into 35 over the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Path Tracer</title>
      <link>https://floriskappeyne.github.io/post/path-tracer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://floriskappeyne.github.io/post/path-tracer/</guid>
      <description>The project I started with my path tracer somewhere in March 2017 and still continue to work on it. At the start of the program, I made a basic ray tracer. A few weeks later I borrowed a book from the library (PBRT, click here to learn more) which made me increase my goal to make a full blown physically based renderer. I followed the basic structure of PBRT for a long time but ultimately I added so many changes of my own that it&amp;rsquo;s not really recognizable anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGR: The Fastest Drifter</title>
      <link>https://floriskappeyne.github.io/post/agr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://floriskappeyne.github.io/post/agr/</guid>
      <description>This video cannot be played.  The project AGR: The Fastest Drifter is an Anti-Gravity Racing game, made with the custom cross-platform (Windows and PS4) Voodoo Rewind Racing Engine. Created by a team of 6 programmers at first (the first block of 8 weeks), and 19 people (7 programmers, 12 designers and artists) at the end, it is one of the biggest projects I have worked on so far. In the end, it featured a fully functioning racing game for both single player and local multiplayer, audio, particle effects, several post processing effects on top of the physically based rendering, a complete game-flow with UI and intro cinematics and a suite of tools usable by designers to tweak the game while playing it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>